# Matin Kahrizi

## **Summary**

I'm a Front-End web developer who enjoys designing and creating wonderful products. I started this journey about 3 years ago and I believe there is no limitations for me to learn new things.

My main expertise is React JS and I daily use React, Webpack, Tailwind Css and Material UI in my projects

# **Work Experience**

**Tafarda** - 05/2021 to 03/2022 **Tehran**, Iran

- At Tafarda company, I was the main Front end developer and we were working on Iranian and European web applications.
- One of the latest applications that we launched, Is called Rsoon.
- In this company I managed to upgrade my knowledge in terms of React also I learned Agile and Scrum systems

**Liteweb** - 02/2020 to 06/2021 **Tehran**, Iran

- At Liteweb company, I was one of the Front end developers and we were working on Freelance projects
- In this company I managed to level-up my JavaScript skills also I learned how to work with Laravel project's structure

#### **Education**

MSc in Computer Science at Shamsipour Technical College (2021- present)
BSc in Computer Science Shamsipour Technical College (2019- 2021)

#### **Skills**

React JS

**Next JS** 

JavaScript Es6+

**Redux / Context** 

**Restful Api** 

Webpack / Babel

**Css / Styled Components** 

**Material UI** 

**Tailwind CSS** 

#### Contact

+98 937 898 5651

https://matinkahrizi.vercel.app matin.kahrizi@gmail.com https://www.github.com/maricoIR

## **Projects**

 You can see all of my projects and access their source code in my website at Here